Yakanton Idol
Now, and the second one...
Strip.
Just by looking at it, you might think I'm a stoic,
Not that I'm not that.
Are you trying to say on dailo?
It's not that I'm stoic,
I'm in love with stoic women.
I like stoic women.
That's what I'm saying.
It has to be me.
That's right.
Originally, when I was little, I liked Yuko Oshima, AKB48,
After that, I left the idol world for a while,
Then, after I left idol group for a while, I joined Master Durst,
After I started working as an idol, I met Mr. Sunao Sakuranao of Team Shachi,
So you fell in love with Mr. Sakuranao.
I see.
And after that, you met Airi Suzuki,
I also fell in love with Airi Suzuki of Hello Project,
I am attracted to women who are stoic and cool.
I am really inspired by them,
They really make you feel alive?
They really make me feel alive.
Really?
They are the reason I am where I am today.
But aren't you attracted to such stoic people, and don't you feel the same way?
No, I don't think of myself as stoic.
Not really.
But I guess I take it for granted.
Yes, I do.
Is that so?
Is it me?
Yes, it is.
It's not me.
Can I say it one more time?
I would like to say something about the people I admire.
That's, you know, stoicism.
What do you mean by that? What do you mean by stoicism?
Mao-chan is really both cool and cute,
She is an idol or a star,
I heard that she keeps a proper schedule.
I don't think she has any lazy days.
I see.
That's right. That's right.
Even in your free time?
Yes, I do. So I don't feel that kind of dase in my private life.
Are there any stoic people other than idols that you are attracted to?
Aya Nakanashi.
I see.
She started her YouTube activity after the Corona disaster.
That's when I really started to like her,
Once an idol starts a movie, they are so busy, aren't they?
But you always update your videos even if you have to fall asleep,
You don't just say, "I'm going to take a break because a new work has started,
I am stoic in the fact that I always finish what I have lent myself to do.
I feel your stoicism in the fact that you always do what you have to do.
When he says, "Oh! I was saying, "Oh!
I think it would be better if you came in and got curious about it.
Are you leaving right now?
Again? Yes.
What aspect of her do you think is stoic?
No, wait a minute.
I said I like stoic people.
Her stoicism is like my own.
I see.
Is that so? Am I stoic?
I never make mistakes.
I don't allow mistakes!
I thought it was not something I could say on my own while listening to this.
Thank you very much.
I always say that I like the relationship with requests,
I would like to have you sit here sometime.
He said he didn't have a signature today.
I don't have one.
Thank you very much.
Okay, thank you very much. Thank you for your time.
It was nice to see a nice painting.
It's fate, now.
I got a call from GET mode.
May I advertise?
This program was provided by Iginari DD Keisuke, Goshashi-Junpei, Yutakuya, Bikyakujin Daijikai Satomi, and Kei-chan.
Thanks everyone!
See you soon!